<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Intro.js Blog</title>
        <link>https://introjs.com/blog</link>
        <description>Intro.js Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <copyright>Copyright © 2020 Usablica Limited</copyright>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Best Tools for Startup Growth Hackers in 2021]]></title>
            <link>https://introjs.com/blog/best-tools-for-startup-growth-hackers-in-2021</link>
            <guid>best-tools-for-startup-growth-hackers-in-2021</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[What makes a startup fail in most cases soon after it commences? The answer is not making its presence known in the required amount of time. That's when growth hacking comes into the picture. Growth hacking has been around for over a decade now. You can call it a branch or type of marketing in one way, but there is one difference between mainstream digital marketing and growth hacking. The focus of growth hacking is simply growth. It does not focus on selling a single product like marketing does at a time. Growth hacking is supposed to be all about creative tactics and carrying out well-thought-out strategies.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Structure a Successful User Onboarding Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://introjs.com/blog/how-to-structure-a-successful-user-onboarding-experience</link>
            <guid>how-to-structure-a-successful-user-onboarding-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A user onboarding experience is a crucial process that determines an important outcome. This process is basically designed for users to go through a responsive guide about a product or software. In a user onboarding experience, a user gets to find out the benefits of the product they’ll be getting. The goal of these programs is to encourage users to opt for a product. Call it an automated form of marketing, but user onboarding experiences can help a user bond with your product or software. It also doesn’t stop after giving the user an overview of the particular product, instead, the user then gets to give their feedback about their overall experience.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Amazing Benefits of User Onboarding You Should Know]]></title>
            <link>https://introjs.com/blog/five-amazing-benefits-of-user-onboarding-you-should-know</link>
            <guid>five-amazing-benefits-of-user-onboarding-you-should-know</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[User onboarding is the most significant part of the digital user experience. If designed carefully, it can eventually result in the user who is becoming your brand's regular user.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[5 Ways to Increase the Free Trial Conversion Rate]]></title>
            <link>https://introjs.com/blog/ways-to-increase-the-free-trial-conversion-rate</link>
            <guid>ways-to-increase-the-free-trial-conversion-rate</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A free trial is sort of a short-lived experience that a consumer gets of your product or service. The goal of this free trial is to encourage the user to buy the product you're selling. Free trials are conducted to give users a short or small taste of whatever you're selling. This can potentially spark interest in the consumer's mind and make them interested in your product or feature. If done correctly, free trials can help you get customers on your side and even get your word out there in public.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[5 Tips for More Engaging Product Tours]]></title>
            <link>https://introjs.com/blog/tips-for-more-engaging-product-tours</link>
            <guid>tips-for-more-engaging-product-tours</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Product tours play a significant role in user onboarding. The goal of product tours is to make people fall in love with your product or feature. You guide them through this process persuade them to take action.]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intro.js v3 🎉]]></title>
            <link>https://introjs.com/blog/introjs-v3</link>
            <guid>introjs-v3</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[I'm more than happy to announce that we have released the Intro.js v3! This version fixes major issues and adds a lot of new features!]]></description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>